（上条(かみじょう)）アニェーゼ？
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）ンッ…
Agnese?
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ちょ…
少々 待ってほしいのでございます
Please, just wait a moment!
あっ… どうして あなたたちが
“アドリア海の女王”に？
Why are you two on The Queen of The Adriatic Sea?
Well...
はぁ… 成り行きで
船に乗ることになったのですけど
We ended up aboard after having gone through some things...
Is The Queen of The Adriatic Sea the name of this ice fleet?
アドリア海の女王というのは―
この氷の艦隊の
名称でございましょうか？
The fleet is called The Queen's Fleet.
艦隊名は “女王艦隊”
この船は護衛艦の１隻
This ship is just one of many.
You really don't know anything about this, do you?
どうやら
ホントに何も知らないみたいですね
What are you doing here?
お前
こんな所で一体 何やってんだ？
I'm helping search for the intruders...
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
侵入者捜索の手伝いですよ
I didn't imagine it'd be you, though.
ですけど まあ
侵入者が あなたたちだったとはね
フフッ…
これは少し利用できそうです
This might work out for me.
We were just dragged into all this!
俺たちだって
巻き込まれたばっかりなんだ
If you keep talking back, I'm going to scream.
グダグダ言ってるようなら
大声出しちまいますよ
If you want to escape, I'd advise you don't upset me.
こっから逃げたいのなら―
私の機嫌を損ねないほうが
いいと思いますけどね
We'll have to do as she says for now.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ひとまず
従うしかないのでございますよ
What benefit is there for you in letting us go?
私たちを逃がして―
あなたに何のメリットが
あるのでございましょう？
A reward.
報酬…
…と
そう受け取ってもらえりゃ結構です
Just think of it that way.
～♪
#15 The Queen's Fleet
So what is The Queen's Fleet?
（上条）
そもそも―
女王艦隊ってのは
一体 何なんだ？
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
まあ アドリア海の監視のために
作られた艦隊なんですけどね
It's a fleet originally created for surveillance purposes on The Adriatic Sea.
I've never heard of such a thing.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
そんな話は聞いたことも
ございませんでしたけど
We tend to know but a small fragment of the entire story.
私たちが知ってる部署なんて
所詮 ほんの一部にすぎやせん
The people on this ship randomly attacked us.
俺たち いきなり
この船のヤツらに襲われたんだぜ
Is this fleet really only for surveillance?
この艦隊 本当に
監視のためだけの施設なのか？
Maybe you literally got caught by our surveillance then.
そりゃ文字どおり 監視に
引っ掛かったんじゃないですか？
You are  the people who ruined the Roman Catholics Church's plans.
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
あなたたちは
ローマ正教のプロジェクトを―
破壊した人物なんですし
On top of that, one of you is Japanese and another is from London.
しかも 片方は日本から
もう片方は
ロンドンから やって来てんです
Well, that's just a cover-up, anyway.
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
まあ それは建て前で
ここは一種の労働施設なんですよ
This is like a labor facility.
They gather criminals, such as myself, and have them repay their debts.
私みてえな罪人を集め―
受けた損失分を
支払わせるためのね
So the people aboard this ship are mainly my squad, or rather, my former squad members.
だから 船にいるのは私の部隊…
いえ 元部隊の
シスターたちが ほとんどです
Let me cut to the chase.
…で こっからが本題です
In return for letting you two go,
あなたたちを
見逃す代わりとして―
I want you to rescue Sister Lucia and Sister Angelene.
シスター･ルチアと
シスター･アンジェレネ
この２人を
ここから助けろってなとこです
あっ… 助けるというのは？
"Rescue"?
Those two used a spell which confuses the security system, allowing them to break out.
あの２人
索敵の裏をかいた術式を使って―
脱獄しちまったんです
They were planning on coming back to get the rest of us, but...
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
彼女たちは 準備を整えてから―
私たちを
助け出そうとしてたみたいですが
（上条）
…で その２人は連れ戻されて
お説教の最中だってのか？
So they were brought back and are in even more trouble now?
I think they're fixing the spell they cast.
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
脱獄術式の防止が先でしょうね
They're probably being modified so they can never use it again.
二度と
その術式を使えなくなるように―
加工されてるでしょうが
（上条）
加工？
Modified?
Do you mean they're making cognitive thought impossible?
それは 思考力そのものを
奪うということでございますか？
In other words, destroying their brain structure?
つまり 脳の構造を砕くと
Please help them before that happens.
そうなる前に
彼女たちを助けてほしい…
That's my only request.
…というのが こちらの願いです
That way we can get the jailbreak spell too.
そうすりゃ
脱獄術式も手に入るでしょう
But doesn't the Roman Catholic Church already know of the spell?
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ですけど その術式は既に―
ローマ正教側にも
バレているのでは？
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
女王艦隊では
これから大仕事があります
The Queen's Fleet has a huge job to do right now.
１人２人の脱獄など
気にしていられないのですよ
They don't have the time to be worrying about one or two escapees.
I'll have to go to the flagship to distract them.
私は陽動のため
旗艦のほうへ行っちまいますが―
Please find them while I do that.
その間に なんとかしてください
You're planning to save us?
お前が助けてくれるってのか？
I'm not saving you. I'm using you.
助けるのではなく
利用するんですがね
You're imprisoned too.
お前だって捕まってんだろう
一緒に逃げようぜ
Let's get out of here together.
The supervisors are afraid of a riot breaking out.
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
管理する側が恐れているのは
労働者の反乱なんです
言っちまえば 私は それを防ぐ―
Let me put it this way:
I'm trying to prevent that from happening.
精神的な
安全装置みてえなもんなんです
I have the right to move freely throughout the fleet.
艦隊の中を
自由に動く権限もありますし
And I don't have to work, either.
労働も免除されています
案外 ここは居心地がいいんですよ
This place is actually kind of comfortable for me.
Sister Lucia and Angelene are both getting nowhere.
シスター･ルチア アンジェレネの
両名は空回りなんですよ
They should have just left us behind...
さっさと自分たちだけで
逃げていればいいものを…
If, by any chance, you escape successfully,
運よく こっから出られたら―
you will no longer be involved with the Roman Catholic Church's activities.
もう二度と ローマ正教には
関わらないことですね
Fine.
分かったよ
But with just us two versus everyone here, there's little chance we'll be able to save them.
多勢に無勢ってなったら
助ける余裕なんかなくなっちまうぞ
This is coming from the man who stood up against an an entire army of Sisters?
以前
あれだけの数のシスター相手に―
１人でケンカを売った男の
セリフですか？
T-Thanks.
（上条）
あ… ありがとう
So those clothes were altered with a spell, limiting you from using magic!
その修道服は 魔術的な
拘束効果を与えるための―
特殊な装飾でございましたか
If that was The Queen's Fleet, I can't do anything alone.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
あれが女王艦隊だとすると
私ひとりで行ってもダメ
No one is around.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）誰もいませんね
（上条）ああ
Yeah. Agnese said it was mostly empty, too.
アニェーゼも
ほとんど無人だって言ってたしな
So that's the room Lucia and Angelene are in?
（上条）
あれか ルチアと
アンジェレネのいる部屋って
うん？　何だ あれ？
What's that?
What is it?
どうしたのでございますか？
なっ… 下がれ オルソラ！
Get back, Orsola!
（上条）
ハァ…
Looks like that armor was some kind of magic construct.
この鎧(よろい)
魔術で動くロボットみたいなものか
Yes. It appears to be a part of the ship, just in a different form.
船の一部が姿を
変えた物のようでございますね
（男性たち）あっ…
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）動くな！
Don't move!
How do you think we broke this?
それ
どうやって壊したと思います？
Oh, my.
あら 思わず日本語のまま
言ってしまいましたけど―
I didn't mean to say that in Japanese.
But you understood me, right?
分かりますよね
警告を聞かないのでしたら
これを使うだけですけど
If you won't heed our warning, we'll just have to use this.
We came to rescue you.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
助けに来たのでございますよ
Do you really think we can believe that?
（ﾙﾁｱ）
そんな言葉を
私たちが信じると思うのですか？
（上条）
え～っとだな…
You see...
According to Agnese, you two had a spell that could get us out of here.
アニェーゼに
話を聞いたかぎりじゃ―
お前たちが こっから出るために
必要な魔術を使えるってことだった
She told us to work with you to escape.
だから お前たちを助けて
協力してもらえって
S-Sister Agnese told you that?!
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
シ…
シスター･アニェーゼにですか？
Use your brain! This could be a trap!
ワナの可能性も少しは考慮なさい
From our point of view, this is enemy territory.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
ここは敵の本拠地
アニェーゼさんの名前を使ってまで
あなたたちを助ける理由は―
Why would we go as far as to use Agnese's name?
想像がつかないのでございますけど
Sister Lucia...
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
シスター･ルチア
I understand. I guess I can trust you this one time.
（ﾙﾁｱ）
分かりました　そちらの言い分にも
一理ぐらいはあるでしょう
So, how do we get out?
ところで
どうやって脱出するんだ？
It's too much trouble to explain it.
説明するのも面倒です
Sister Angelene.
（ﾙﾁｱ）シスター･アンジェレネ
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）あっ え～っと…
Wow...
（上条）
すげえ
By modifying the spell that turns these ships into ice, we can easily create a hole.
（ﾙﾁｱ）
氷を使った造船術式の亜種で
空洞を開けられるのです
We can utilize this to harden sea water into a small pod.
これを応用し 海水を固めて―
海底コースターを
作り上げることができます
（２人）アアッ！
（上条）あっ どうした？
What's wrong?
They added an countermagic spell to our clothes, too...
や… やっぱり 拘束衣服にも
迎撃術式を追加されたようですね
If we undo the sewing in a certain way, we can reduce certain restrictions.
手順にのっとって縫い目を壊せば
拘束機能の一部は壊せます
Undo?
壊す？　うん？
なあ
だったら 手っとり早く 俺の…
Then how about we just use my—
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
まあまあ　まさか彼女たちまで―
Oh, my, do you plan on stripping these two as well?
素っ裸に
するつもりでございましょうか？
What's going to happen to us now?
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
私たち これから
どうなっちゃうんでしょうか
Rather...
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
それよりも―
I'm more interested in what today's dinner is going to be.
今日の晩ご飯のほうが
気になっているんですけど
What do you mean? There's nothing more important than the Lord in this world...
（ﾙﾁｱ）
どういうことですか？
この世界に主より重要なものなど…
Me, too!
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
わ… 私も気になります
もう３日連続で
隠し味がオリーブばかりで…
They've been using old olives to add a little flavoring for three days straight.
あっ あと
お風呂も ちょっと 熱すぎますよね
The bath is a little hot, too!
Who cares about the flavoring?
隠し味など どうでもいいのです
And the bath's lukewarm, not hot.
それに あの浴場は
少し ぬるいくらいでしょう
Really?
そ… そうでしょうか？
Well it's true that the adults don't seem to care much...
確かに 大人の方たちは
あまり気にしてないような…
But then—
そうすると… ウッ…
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）ハァ…
（ﾙﾁｱ）どうかしましたか？
What's wrong?
If you're going to talk to them, I'll go with you.
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
じ… 直談判(じかだんぱん)なら私も ご一緒します
Yeah.
そうですね
それも いいかもしれませんね
That might be good, too.
When will we rendezvous with Sister Agnese?
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
シスター･アニェーゼとは
いつ合流できるんですか？
Sorry.
（上条）悪い
（ﾙﾁｱ･ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）うん？
Agnese probably isn't coming.
アニェーゼは 多分 来ない
She said she was going to distract everyone so that we can escape.
お前たちを助けるために
陽動に出るって言ってた
この女王艦隊の
旗艦に行ってるらしいけど
She's apparently going to the flagship of The Queen's Fleet.
あっ… 冗談ではありません！
You've got to be kidding!
This Queen's Fleet was created for the sole purpose
この女王艦隊は大規模魔術
of protecting the magic circle of the great spell "Queen of the Adriatic Sea."
“アドリア海の女王”の
儀式場を守るためのものです
（上条）
アドリア海の女王？
Queen of the Adriatic Sea?
分かっているのは
同名の旗艦で行われること
All we know is that it's activated on the flagship with the same name.
Another spell, called the Appointed Time of the Rosary, is related to its activation.
その発動キーとして
“刻限のロザリオ”という―
別の術式が関わっていること
And Agnese is going to be used for the Appointed Time of the Rosary.
そして 刻限のロザリオに―
シスター･アニェーゼが
使われるってことです
あっ…
ア… アニェーゼは どうなるんだ？
What will happen to Agnese?
We don't know much about the plan.
（ﾙﾁｱ）
詳細は私たちにも分かりません
But her brain will be completely destroyed, leaving only her heart beating.
ですが 少なくとも
脳は確実に破壊され―
心臓を動かすだけの存在になると…
The Queen's Fleet has a huge job to do right now.
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
女王艦隊では
これから大仕事があります
They don't have the time to be worrying about one or two escapees.
１人２人の脱獄など
気にしていられないのですよ
An attack?
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
こ… 攻撃… でも どこから？
Where from?
It can't be... It's coming from allied ships...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
まさか 同じ味方艦から…
St. Barbara's Holy Cannon?
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
聖(セント)バルバラの神砲？
What are you shooting at?
一体 何に向けて撃ってるんです？
（ﾋﾞｱｰｼﾞｵ）
分からないのか？
シスター･アニェーゼ
You don't get it, Sister Agnese?
Bishop Biagio...
（ｱﾆｪｰｾﾞ）
ビショップ･ビアージオ…
Ship number 37 has been sunk.
（男性Ａ）
37番艦は沈みました
We will hit land if we continue to fire.
これ以上の砲撃は
陸からの干渉も…
（ﾋﾞｱｰｼﾞｵ）
人目の処理は
よその部署に回しておけ
Leave PR cleanup to my subordinates.
That work doesn't interest me.
私の管轄ではない
If something were to happen to your body, we wouldn't be able to recover it.
（ﾋﾞｱｰｼﾞｵ）
君の身に何かあったら
取り返しがつかないだろう
Ironic, isn't it?
皮肉なものですね
The Appointed Time of the Rosary...
刻限のロザリオ
Who would have thought that a heretic like yourself would be the only one compatible with it...
まさか 術式の適正を―
背信者の君だけが持っているとはな
We have an emergency, Bishop Biagio!
（男性Ｂ）
ビショップ･ビアージオ 緊急です
What?
（ﾋﾞｱｰｼﾞｵ）何だ？
（男性Ｂ）はっ！
A large construct has been detected beneath the position where ship 37 was sunk.
（男性Ｂ）
37番艦の下部に
巨大構造物の反応あり
It appears to be salvaging the remains.
（男性Ｂ）
残骸を回収しているもよう
An underwater spell?
潜水術式…
What happened to everyone?
オルソラたちは…
This is bad...
（上条）
マズイ…
I might seriously die...
（上条）
これは… 本当に死ぬかも
当麻！
Touma!
（上条）
ンンッ… インデックス…
Index?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
体は平気なの？　当麻
Are you okay, Touma?
（上条）た… 建宮斎字(たてみや さいじ)か？
（建宮）おう
T-Tatemiya Saiji?
Yep, the substitute Pope of the Amakusa Church.
天草(あまくさ)式十字凄教(せいきょう)の教皇代理さんだ
今は手前に
イギリス清教所属って つくけどよ
Though, now we're affiliated with the Church of England.
（上条）うん？
（五和(いつわ)）どうぞ
Here.
Oh, thanks.
（上条）ああ どうも
（五和）いえいえ
No problem.
Wait, why are you guys here?
つうか なんで こんな所に？
オルソラたちは？
Where's Orsola?
Well, we managed to pick all of you up.
（建宮）
まあ 一応 全員拾っておいたのよ
We're interrogating the men who were on board elsewhere, though.
男たちのほうには
別で話を聞いてるがな
I see...
そっか
So is this some secret Amakusa Church base?
…で ここって天草式の
秘密基地みたいなもんなのか？
This isn't a building.
ここは建物じゃねえのよな
ああ？　てことは まさか…
No way, is this—
I'd call it a submarine, but it's not that fancy.
（建宮）
潜水艦と言いたいところだが―
そこまで高性能じゃねえ
It's more like a wooden ship that can go underwater.
せいぜい
潜航機能のついた木船ってのに近い
A ship that can both float and sink.
まあ 上下艦ってやつよ
You guys brought along something like this to help with the moving?
（上条）
引っ越しの手伝いするのに
こんな物 持ってくるのか？
We'd obviously keep our weapons on hand.
（建宮）
我らが武器を懐に持つのは当たり前
And, in case you didn't know, our specialty is naval combat.
そして
我々が最も得意とするのは 海戦よ
Paper is made from trees, and ships are made from wood.
紙は木で作られ
木は船をも作るってな
Agnese...
（上条）アニェーゼ…
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ンンッ…
あっ な… 何だよ？
Wh-What is it?
Nothing.
別に…
これから どうするにしても―
Before we discuss what to do now, you need to explain what's been going on.
まずは詳しい話を聞かないとね
なら 俺より
ルチアとかアンジェレネのほうが…
Wouldn't it be better for Lucia and Angelene to do that?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）ンンッ…
（上条）…て あれ？
Er... what?
Looks like you guys made it here safely, too.
そっちも無事だったみたいだな
うん？
You don't have to be so shy, now.
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
もう そんなに
恥ずかしがらなくてもよろしいのに
この２人の修道服は
ローマ正教が用意した拘束装飾でな
Those Sisters' uniforms were binding garments created by the church.
While you were sleeping, we used your right hand to destroy them.
（上条）はぁ？
（建宮）そいつをぶっ壊すため―
お前さんが気絶してる間に
右手を使わせてもらったってわけ
Eh?
That means...
（上条）
てことは…
Yep.
（建宮）
そういうことなのよな
当麻～！
Touma!
こ… これで怒られるのは…
G-Getting angry at me for that is so unfair!
（上条）
理不尽だ～！
Oh, right!
あっ そうでした
こんなことをしている場合では…
We don't have time for this!
Sister Agnese is still...?
あ… あの…
シスター･アニェーゼが まだ…
That's just wrong!
You have such a strong bite, so why are you unable to defend yourself against magicians?!
私たちには まだ目的があって
できれば―
We still have a job to do!
We need to go free Sister Agnese and—
シスター･アニェーゼのことを
説明…
Your bite is way more effective than the 103,000 grimoires in your head!
（上条）
10万3,000冊より それで戦えば…
（五和）ウワッ！
（悲鳴）
This is your chance, Itsuwa!
（天草式Ａ）
五和 チャンスだ いけ！
Go for it!
Nip him on the earlobe!
（天草式Ｂ）
耳たぶにチュッと やってしまえ！
だから 現状の説明を…
I'm trying to explain the situation...
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
あら まあ…
Oh, my!
This is getting interesting.
（建宮）
こりゃ 面白くなってきたのよ
お願いですから聞いてください！
ウウ～ッ…
Please listen to me!
Attention!
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
注目！
S-Sister Angelene?
（ﾙﾁｱ）
シ… シスター･アンジェレネ…
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
ぶ… 部隊内では いつも
こんな感じだったじゃないですか
We always did stuff like that in our group, so out of habit I accidentally...
だから あの… いつもの癖で…
（建宮）
うん？　いつも？
"Always"?
I prefer chocolate cream over coffee or tea.
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
私は コーヒーとか紅茶よりも―
チョコラータ･コン･パンナが
いいです
（上条）
なに それ？
What's that?
It's hot chocolate with lots of cream on top—
チョコレートドリンクの上に
生クリームが たっ…
Sister Angelene! A Christian should not have such obsessions over food!
シスター･アンジェレネ
十字教徒が食べ物に執着など…
（上条）まあまあ
（五和）あの…
Um... here.
（五和）
どうぞ
Oh, thanks.
あっ… ああ どうも
Not at all.
The hot towel plan again, Itsuwa?
（天草式Ａ）
また おしぼり作戦なのか？　五和
（天草式Ｂ）
ええい まどろっこしい！
This is going too slowly!
No, her complete lack of progress is part of her charm!
（天草式Ｃ）
いや こうなかなか進展しないのも
五和の魅力なのでは？
So why is that spell called The Queen of The Adriatic Sea?
（上条）
でも なんでアドリア海の女王が
術式の名前になってんだ？
Long ago, the Venetian and Roman Catholic Churches used to be enemies.
その昔
ヴェネチアとローマ正教は―
相当に
仲が悪かったのでございますよ
The Roman Catholic Church created The Queen of The Adriatic Sea in order to erase Venice in one blow.
ローマ正教が一撃でヴェネチアを
葬れるように整えたのが―
アドリア海の女王なんだよ
葬るって
爆弾みたいなものなのか？
Erase? So it's like a bomb?
破壊されるだけじゃない
It doesn't just destroy.
It has the power to make the culture and history of the city completely disappear.
その町の文化や歴史そのものまで
全部 奪われるの
Everything...
全部？
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
シスター･アニェーゼは
きっと何も知らないと思います
Sister Agnese probably isn't aware of that.
If she knew, there's no way she'd have kept silent.
知っていれば
絶対に黙っているはずがありません
So, basically, we have to rescue Agnese Sanctis before they can start up that spell.
（建宮）
要は
その魔術が発動するまでに―
アニェーゼ＝サンクティスを
連れ戻せってんだろうけど―
But that's going to be extremely difficult.
まあ とんでもなく難問よな
Even so, we must do it.
それでも 行かなくてなりません
If we don't, Sister Agnese will become crippled.
このままでは―
シスター･アニェーゼは
廃人になってしまいます
Are you saying we should just sit by and let that happen?
それを
黙って見てろというのですか？
Sister Agnese has always saved me in the past,
私は いつも―
シスター･アニェーゼに
助けてもらっていたから―
so I can't just forget about her without repaying her!
何も返せないまま お別れなんて
絶対にイヤです！
The enemy is strong, you know?
だが 敵は やっかいだぜ
If we dispatch underwater pods everywhere we might be able to stop their movement!
海底コースターを張り巡らせれば
艦隊の動きを止められるかも
You can't be so naive as to think simply stopping them will be enough.
動きを止めた程度で
なんとかなる相手とも思えんのよな
W-Well...
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）
そ… それは…
Hey, Tatemiya. Isn't that enough already?
（上条）
なあ 建宮 もういいんじゃねえのか
Huh?
What we should be discussing isn't whether or not to save Agnese.
俺たちが議論すべきなのは―
アニェーゼを助けたいか
助けたくないかっていう―
それだけなんじゃねえのか
She ignored her own opportunity to escape, in order to help set her friends free.
（上条）
あいつは自分が助かるチャンスを
わざわざ 棒に振って―
仲間を逃がそうとした
If we don't move, her feelings are going to be used and then broken.
このままじゃ―
あいつの思いは誰かに
利用されたまま 破壊されちまう
We just need to save her, right?
（上条）
要は
あいつを助けりゃいいんだろう？
If we do that, we'll be protecting Venice from destruction at the same time.
ヴェネチアの破壊だって
それで全部 防げるんだろう？
Then we only have one road before us!
（上条）
だったら
やることは１つじゃねえか
Don't you want to save her?
お前は
あいつを助けたくないのかよ？
If you don't, I'll go myself!
だったら
俺は１人でも あそこに行くぞ！
（上条）あっ…
（建宮）…たく
Geez...
As far as I'm concerned, that part of the discussion was already over.
こっちとしちゃ
そこは最初からクリアしてんだ
I've already prepared a plan.
策なら 初めから用意してあるのよ
（上条）えっ？
I just wanted to see whether you really had the resolve or not.
覚悟があるかどうか
聞きたかっただけなのよな
Tatemiya...
建宮…
Listen up!
いいか！
我らが戦場に向かうからには―
We are going to enter the field of battle and come back alive!
必ず生きて帰る
What did the High Priestess teach us?
我らが女教皇(プリエステス)から得た教えは？
To reach out to those in need!
（天草式たち）
救われぬ者に救いの手を！
Here you go.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）はい これ
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）あっ… まあ
Oh, my...
I can't use it, so it'll probably be more useful to you.
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
私には使えないから
あなたが持っていたほうがいいかも
あっ…
うん？
な… 何だよ インデックス
Wh-What is it, Index?
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）
別に
Nothing.
Let's get started.
では 始めんのよ
（ｱｶﾞﾀｰ）
あっ… ビショップ･ビアージオ
Bishop Biagio!
Approaching ships detected! Around 30 to 40.
接近する船影 30から40
本艦の座標まで50秒弱
A little less than 50 seconds until they reach us!
Sink them!
（ﾋﾞｱｰｼﾞｵ）沈められるか？
（ｱｶﾞﾀｰ）了解
Understood.
１発も撃ってこない
They aren't shooting back at all...
Could it be...
まさか… 総員 防御姿勢！
All hands, defensive positions!
（ﾋﾞｱｰｼﾞｵ）
どうした？
What's happening?
Drones!
火船です
自爆を前提とした無人艦隊です！
They're unmanned explosive boats!
There is a large construct approaching at a depth of 40 meters!
（ｱｶﾞﾀｰ）
深度40メートルに巨大構造物
恐らく上下艦です！
It is likely a submarine!
Confirmed hit on the submarine!
（男性Ａ）上下艦への着弾を確認！
（男性Ｂ）第29番艦に敵戦力！
Ship 29 is being boarded!
It's the Amakusa forces from before!
例の天草式です！
まさか… 上下艦も囮(おとり)！
No way... the submarine was a decoy too?!
Don't worry about taking over each ship!
（建宮）
各艦の制圧は考えるな！
All you have to think about is destroying the enemy core!
相手の核だけ
つぶすことを考えればいいのよな
（建宮）
お前さんたちは
“アドリア海の女王”へ
You guys head for The Queen of The Adriatic Sea.
Got it.
Hurry!
急げ！
（破壊音）
Index!
（上条）インデックス！
（ｲﾝﾃﾞｯｸｽ）アア…
（ﾙﾁｱ）こちらへ！
（上条）分かった！
This way!
Okay!
（ﾙﾁｱ）
このバカどもが！
These idiots...
Why aren't you helping to save Sister Agnese?
なぜシスター･アニェーゼを
助けるために動けない？
（上条）
アア… 撃ってきた！
They're firing at us!
They're trying to sink us along with the entire ship!
（ｵﾙｿﾗ）
私たちごと沈める気では？
They shot right at us...
（ﾙﾁｱ）こっちを直接狙って？
（ｼｽﾀｰ）そんな…
No way...
Come out, one of the twelve disciples...
来たれ 十二使徒のひとつ
debt collector, eradicator of magicians, and lowly servant!
徴税吏にして 魔術師を討ち滅ぼす
卑賤(ひせん)なるしもべよ！
This is bad...
マズイ！　ンンッ！
Come out, one of the twelve disciples?
来たれ 十二使徒のひとつ
Watch out!
（ｱﾝｼﾞｪﾚﾈ）危ない！
（ｼｽﾀｰＡ）アッ…
Sister Angelene!
（ﾙﾁｱ）シスター･アンジェレネ！
（上条）あっ…
Sister Angelene!
（ﾙﾁｱ）
シスター･アンジェレネ！
～♪
Next Episode
（上条）
“アドリア海の女王”の
発動を止めるため―
We board the flagship to stop The Queen of The Adriatic Sea from activating.
俺たちは旗艦へと乗り込む
As more and more questions remain unanswered, how does Index act?
次々と判明する新たな謎に
インデックスは…
次回 「刻限のロザリオ」
Next time: "Appointed Time of the Rosary."
When science and magic cross paths, this epic will begin!
科学と魔術が交差するとき
物語は始まる